promovouchers.co.uk 2016-02-19

# Privacy & Cookies - Promo Vouchers

1.    Introduction  
1.1    We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; in this policy we explain how we will treat your personal information.  
1.2    By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

2.    Collecting personal information  
2.1    We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:   
(a)    information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths);  
(b)    information that you provide to us when registering with our website (including your email address);  
(c)    information that you provide when completing your profile on our website (including your name, profile pictures, gender, date of birth, relationship status, interests and hobbies, educational details and employment details];  
(d)    information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters (including your name and email address);  
(e)    information that you provide to us when using the services on our website, or that is generated in the course of the use of those services ;  
2.2    Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must obtain that person’s consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in accordance with this policy.

3\.    Using your personal information  
3.1    Personal information submitted to us through our website will be used for the purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the website.  
3.2    We may use your personal information to:   
(a)    administer our website and business;  
(b)    personalise our website for you;  
(c)    enable your use of the services available on our website;  
(d)    send you goods purchased through our website;  
(e)    supply to you services purchased through our website;  
(f)    send statements, invoices and payment reminders to you, and collect payments from you;  
(g)    send you non-marketing commercial communications;  
(h)    send you email notifications that you have specifically requested;  
(i)    send you our email newsletter, if you have requested it (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require the newsletter);  
(j)    send you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you, by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);  
(k)    provide third parties with statistical information about our users (but those third parties will not be able to identify any individual user from that information);  
(l)    deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to our website; and  
(m)   keep our website secure and prevent fraud  
3.3    If you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the licence you grant to us.

4.    Disclosing personal information  
4.1    We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.  
4.2    We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.  
4.3    We may disclose your personal information:   
(a)    to the extent that we are required to do so by law;  
(b)    in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;  
(c)    in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);  
(d)    to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset that we are (or are contemplating) selling; and  
(e)    to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.  
4.4    Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information to third parties.

5.    Updating information  
5.1    Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

6.1 Introduction to Cookie Policy  
Our website uses cookies. By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

6.2   About cookies  
A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a website and identify users returning to a website.

We don’t allow Google to use or share our analytics data. Google Analytics sets the following cookies:

Name| Purpose| Expires  
---|---|---  
_utma| Determines the number of unique visitors to the site| 2 years  
_utmb| This works with _utmc to calculate the average length of time you spend on our site| 30 minutes  
_utmc| This works with _utmb to calculate when you close your browser| when you close your browser  
_utmz| This provides information about how you reached the site (eg from another website or a search engine)| 6 months  
GDS_successEvents and GDS_analyticsTokens| These help us identify how you use DiscountCodeGirl so we can make the site better| 4 months  
  
### YouTube videos

We use YouTube to provide videos on some pages of the site. YouTube sets cookies when you visit one of these pages.

Name| Purpose| Expires  
---|---|---  
_use_hitbox| This is a randomly generated number that identifies your browser| When you close your browser  
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE| Lets Youtube count the views of embedded Youtube videos| 9 months
